

DESIGN

PHOTOSHOP

C4D + OCTANE

ILLUSTRATOR

AFTER EFFECTS

LIGHTROOM

DEVELOPMENT

HTML

Css

JAVASCRIPT

REACT.JS

NODE.JS

SASS

JQUERY

MONGODB

EDUCATION

PALO VERDE HIGH SCHOOL LAS VEGAS, NV

MWW.AARONLILLA.COM

SUMMARY

2.5 years professional exposure in JavaScript technology such as React JS, MongoDB, Express.js and Node JS.

8+ years of professional exposure to HTML, CSS, and Photoshop

Experience with Flux, Babel+ES6, EXT JS and WebPack for Single Page Application development.

Expertise in creating the user validation forms and using the RESTful services for sending the data to the server.

Experience working with CSS Background, padding, table, Animations, Pseudo classes and Layouts, positioning, border, margin, Pseudo elements and CSS behaviors including the Box model.

Experience with the version controls GIT, GITHUB, Package manager NPM, Bower.

WORK EXPERIENCE

06/2010 TO CURRENT

FREELANCE WEB DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

- Planned, developed, tested, deployed, and maintained web applications
- Effectively translated client requirements into application designs and system requirements
- 8 years UX/UI & HTML/CSS
- 2.5 Years Full-stack Javascript experience with MERN (MongoDB, Express, React, NodeJS)
- Creating logos, banners and buttons for websites
- The back-end use of Node JS, Express JS, MongoDB and Mongoose, the complete MERN Stack to provide RESTful API.
- Experience creating multiple CRUD (Create, Read, Update, Delete) applications
- Implemented generating the verification hash code using Node JS and added user validations and user permissions by using Node JS.
- Created React JS reusable components (multi-field form elements), background file uploads.
- Extensively used GIT for version controlling and regularly pushed the code to GitHub
- Developed cross browser/platform HTML 4/5, CSS 3, and JavaScript to match design specs for complex page layouts while adhering to code standards.
- Worked with clients and senior user experience designers to understand the branding strategies and design goals to define strategy, layout and features for the web sites/applications design.
- Developed HTML prototype and UI deliverable such as wireframes, screen mock-ups and interface design.

05/2017 TO CURRENT

EVERGREEN ORGANIX

SUPERCRITICAL CO2 EXTRACTION CHEMIST

- Responsible for start to finish supercritical extraction of organic matter into high quality concentrate
- lacksquare Distill crude concentrate using short path distillation
- \blacksquare Responsible for production run design to min-max yields depending on product quality
- Created Standard Operating Procedures and safety standards for main laboratory

02/2015 TO 05/2017

EVERGREEN ORGANIX INVENTORY & PACKAGING MANAGER

- Responsible for tracking and maining a multi-million dollar inventory in a very fast paced environment
- Fulfilling and directing shipping of large orders
- Maintained software for tracking inventory as well as back-end system maintenance
- Managed a team of 6 successfully and improved overall efficiency

PERSONAL PROJECTS

SYNTHESIS WWW.SYNTHESIS.GG A unique way to watch your favorite live game streamers who are playing in the same game instance, at the same time, together

ROCK & STONE ROCKANDSTONE

A websocket (socket.io) based online matchmaking system for the game Deep Rock Galactic